The way back begins with a single chord.
Rudderless is a music, drama, comedy film directed by William H. Macy.
A grieving father in a downward spiral stumbles across a box of
his recently deceased son's demo tapes and lyrics.
Shocked by the discovery of this unknown talent, he forms a
band in the hope of finding some catharsis.
Sam Manning, played by Billy Crudup.
Quentin, played by Anton Yelchin.
Emily, played by Felicity Huffman.
Kate Lucas, played by Selena Gomez.
Josh Manning, played by Miles Heizer.
Mary Beth, played by Alexandra Lovelace.
Rudderless is a 2014 American musical drama film which
was the directorial debut of William H.
Macy, and stars Billy Crudup, Anton Yelchin, Felicity
Huffman, Selena Gomez and Laurence Fishburne.
The film premiered at the 2014 Sundance Film Festival on January 24, 2014.
The film was released in theaters and through
video-on-demand beginning October 17, 2014.
The film explores themes of parent child relationship, rock
band, mourning, grieving father, reflective.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.